I got a new catsuit from rubber bunny and it's literally a catsuit because
it's a cat suit, cat costume with an inflatable tail so my first latex piece
with an inflatable something and there are also cat ears. Alright before I'm going to
oh these are cat ears by the way, before I'm going to put it on I have to inflate
the tail. So oh and there are gloves too. I love the design it's very very special we have
different latex colors so black transparent and black and gold and silver elements and this is
the tail which I have to inflate now and I have to do that from the inside that's why it's important
I do this first. Oh and by the way it's a neck entry so a lot is happening here.
So this is how the tail looks from the inside and there is a hole and I have this pump which
kind of looks like a syringe. All right and now I'm going to pump.
So this is the tail.
I think it's very funny.
Kind of reminds me of the balloon animals.
I'm going to get dressed off camera because it's a 0.4mm neck entry and also I need to
insert these because it's also a big boob catsuit so so much going on here inflatable
latex big boob neck entry awesome design well see you in a sec
Not gonna lie squeezing into a 0.4mm neck entry catsuit is definitely not my favorite
thing to do but I managed to get into it and now I'm wearing this catsuit and the
tail is still standing and going strong it touches my legs when I move around
which also makes funny sounds and as it is the cyber cat catsuit of course I
have to put on the ears there are a lot of extraordinary details about this
catsuit we have these resin wait where's one there we have this 3d resin parts
that are glued onto the catsuit we have a bunch of them here are some there are
some in the back are some in the neck then there is the rubber bunny logo here
which is head cut and when I say rubber bunny I mean that because it is a bunny
that is wearing a rubber suit which is so cute so there are care instructions
coming with the catsuit like a little comic really cute and I didn't notice
that at first but you'll cut out in the back is heart-shaped Oh heart and also
we have these white stripes here and I also like the keyhole cut here and yeah
the tail of course so there's a lot going on I put on the silicon inlays which are
around about 1000 gram per side which is a lot so I have like the real life jiggle physics
it always gets me with the tail I also have some gloves which I'm going to put on now and I also
put on some shoes but open-toe shoes so you can still see the socks the
integrated socks there we go I love how they fit with the catsuit because they
also have this golden stripe here so round and round matchy matchy also with
the tail. The cat seat is 100% made to measure and if you want to order it
bring some time because the measurement sheet is quite extensive and you have to
fill out a lot of measurements get someone to help you to take these
measurements that's my tip and also they can fully customize the cups so I
measured my inlays and said hey these are the ones I want to use and they
They make the cups according to my silicone inlays, which is great.
But of course, you don't have to use silicone inlays.
You can also just tell them your measurements for your natural boobs.
And it also works.
But I think I quite like the look with the fake boobs.
Because, I mean, it's a cat with an inflatable tail.
So why not some boobs too?
You can also customize the colors.
and I beg you to have a look at the webshop because there are so many cool
costumes there. For example the kitty maid suit with also lots of details or
the sacred nun set with so many pieces and I think it's a great design haven't
seen it like this somewhere else. There's also the chocolate desire set which is
quite a funny name I think or the Miranda latex suit which I also like so
please please have a look at the shop I will link everything in the description
text I have to say I am a big fan of the black transparent latex I really don't
like the natural transparent yellowish latex color but black transparent is a
really cool color especially in combination with the black and also with
the cold so it doesn't look too naked but you can show skin while wearing
latex that's the awesome thing about to see through colors here and of course I
also love the ears I think they definitely have to be part of the outfit
if you have a tail you also need ears I want to try how to sit with the tail
I'm getting the stool and then I don't know I'll just take all of the tail and sit.
So since the tail is pretty high on my back it's not really a problem to sit because it's
over my bum.
I'm not sitting on the tail.
I can just put it on the stool like this.
So there's no air loss in the tail and when I tried it for the first time to inflate it
I was like okay how do I get the air out of it again?
And I found out that you can detach the needle part here and then you have to push that through
the valve and through the needle the air will be released again.
Alright, thanks to Rubber Bunny for sending me this suit and for providing me with my
first inflatable latex piece.
So that definitely was a first for me.
I know that there are some crazy designs out there with more inflatable stuff but I think
the tail is a very cute option and it's not too complicated and not in the way.
So yeah, check out the Rubber Bunny link I put in the description text, check out my
other videos on my channel. Check out my Patreon for behind the scenes and additional content.
I hope you enjoyed this video. I hope you liked the cat as much as I did. And give it
a thumbs up. I will see you in the next video. Have a nice day. Bye.